Rival Sisters. Challenge of a Lifetime. Let the Games Begin!
The Challenge is a adventure, comedy, family film directed by Craig Shapiro.
Estranged twins Lizzie and Shane are chosen for a Survivor-like
popular game show with college scholarships as the prize.
Elizabeth "Lizzie" Dalton, played by Ashley Olsen.
Shane Dalton, played by Mary-Kate Olsen.
Adam, played by Lukas Behnken.
Marcus, played by Brian Skala.
Anthony, played by Theo Rossi.
Kelly, played by Sarah Bastian.
The Challenge is a 2003 comedy film starring Mary-Kate and Ashley
Olsen, their final direct-to-video production.
It was the  last of seven direct-to-video films produced
by Tapestry Films to star the Olsens.
The film explores themes of sibling relationship, competition, twins.
The tone is lighthearted.